Hi everyone so in today's video we are going to discuss how to take content
for your profile. This has been highly highly requested so the mentors L and
myself have put together this video to show you how to take content for your
profile. So first let's talk about why it's important to have good content on
your profile. First of all your profile photo is what your client see. That's
the
first thing they see is your profile photo so you really want that to be as
eye-catching and intriguing as possible and we'll go into some steps on how to
do that a little bit later in the video. And secondly you can actually make
money
with your content. You can sell photos and sell videos and sell album bundles
to
your clients and they're always there available to purchase so more and more
clients can keep buying them over time. So a little bit of effort that you're
putting now to take the content can be on your profile for as long as you want
and you can keep making money from that. So it's really worth putting some good
content on your profile for those reasons. So you're going to want your
profile photo to be quite eye-catching and you also want to think about what
type of what type of energy you want to give off in the photo. Do you want to
be
inviting? Do you want to be confident? Do you want to be dominating? Do you
want to
come across as quite submissive? You know try and tell a story in your profile
photo of what type of experience the clients can have with you. That way you're
more likely to attract the type of clients that you want. And in your
gallery photos here you can have an array of different photos potentially to
attract different types of clients. So for example you might be the girl next
door so you might have some you know just cute photos some innocent type
photos in there but then you could have a photo of your feet and this would
attract
full clients so you'll attract guys who are into the girl next door and also
guys who are into full footage. You're appearing to more clients and in the
free gallery you're gonna want to just try and entice the clients in to buy
your private gallery so you don't want to put anything to reveal and in the
free
gallery on AdultWork it's not actually allowed either. You have to have your
profile photo and pre-gallery photos they can have no nudity or anything like
that. They have to be safe for work as they call it but then your private
gallery you can save that for the more revealing ones and for any nudity and
this is allowed in there and you can try and use your free gallery to have
people
buy your private gallery. So in the private gallery you can also create some
albums. You could have an album dedicated just to an oil album and it could be
photos of you rubbing oil in different parts of your body. You can even do a
video like this to sell as well. Of course you can be as clothed or as
naked as you want to be. You could have an album with an ice cream,
eat an ice cream, let it drift down on you. This is one of the mentors ideas.
So yeah there are some creative ways that you can do content for your profile
rather than just being the normal photos in lingerie or bikini or whatnot.
You can get creative with props as well. Speaking of getting creative one of
the
mentors Chloe actually shared some photos with us which I'm going to cue next
that she done using the light and shadows against the wall
and it's her silhouette. So she said this might be good for the Shire girls who
don't want to necessarily take photos of themselves right away.
Maybe they feel a bit shy to be you know semi-naked on photos.
So this way you don't actually see you. You just see your silhouette against
the reflection on the wall and it's really beautiful how it turned out.
So I'll show it next in this video.
So you can play with that as well. So let's talk about colours and the
background. So you want to keep the background
as clear as possible. For example if I was taking content here
I would remove the bike, I'd remove the table,
I just removed some, I'd remove a lot of the stuff so it was nice and clear.
But for the purpose of this video I didn't but if I was taking content from
my profile I definitely would. I wouldn't want too much clutter in the
background. You also have to make sure there are no
people, pets or photos in the background that's not allowed.
So yeah just keep the space nice and open and inviting if possible.
Another thing you could do is if your background, if you don't want it in the
shot or you know you're not able to have a clear background maybe there's too
much stuff or photos on the wall you can't take down.
You could even use an AI background if that's done well it can actually look
really really good. And talking about the colours you could
wear, something really bright and eye-catching for your profile photo.
One of the mentors said that she's never done better than the time when she had
a
photo with she had a red lingerie set on and a red lip
and she felt like she got so much traffic because of that.
What you can also do is is you can add a red border to your photo
and that also can attract people in because red,
the colour red is meant to make people want to spend.
Another thing to consider is lighting. Now I would always choose natural
lighting
if possible but you can also create some nice shots
with a backlight behind the camera and a second light so to say on this side.
I don't know what the technical name is. A light on this side to then
create some like dimension and depth in the photo and I'm going to show that
when I go upstairs in a moment. But at the minute I'm outside with natural
light
and I really like in the light of this shot but I am going to show how it would
look now in a different light. So right now I'm standing under a light
and as you can see the frame is completely different
so I would not want to take photos in this light to be honest.
I'd must prefer the light. I was under downstairs for natural light
but I just wanted to show how the different lighting can affect
how it looks. Something else important to note
is angles so the angle will make or break the shot basically.
I'm sure we've all picked up our phones and it's been open on the front camera
and we're just looking down like and you know just the most unflattering angle
and or we can like you know change the angle and suit us to how
we feel comfortable in and really enjoy the shot.
So yeah the angles can make a big difference and I'm going to show upstairs
some different angles that you can do to take photos for your profile.
One of the mentors Sophie gave a point that when taking the content
it's good to use the best app on your phone which takes photos every
couple of seconds so you can set it to take five photos every five seconds
and then you can get into a pose and then change the pose for the next one
so you've got quite a lot of photos in one go. It just makes it easier than
having
to do it every time and on that note it'd probably be good
to actually set a day or you know a couple of hours in a day to do
content so for example you'll get yourself
all done up like however feels good to you like to your hair or makeup however
you like it put on an outfit that you like
and then just give yourself a few hours to take content for your profile.
You could put on some music you can put on a candle some incense
you know you can put some body oil on like whatever it is that would make you
feel good get yourself in that headspace
and then you can take the content for your profile
and then as Sophie said you can use that time app
get a lot in one go but yeah while you're there while you're all
while you've got yourself in your outfit and all ready to go
you may as well do quite a lot at once just so then you've got
an abundance of content that you can post over time
you know you can spend a couple of hours doing it and that could get you that
could
get your mum's worth of content you can even do videos as well
like we mentioned so now let's move on to actually
taking the content so let's check the space
so as you can see I have nothing in the background not pictures
or not much clutter I have the backlight that I spoke about
and I also have my phone attached to a ring light
I think it's good to have a bright light on you and then
a different light in the background just to give a little bit of dimension to
the shot I also have this light that I
normally use for cam actually I clip it onto my laptop
it's a good one for cam you can add this in as well I can click it onto the
curtain because it's able to do that or I could just set it down on the
bed and angle it so you can play around with different light
and see how that works as you can see it does give
a different look to the shot for example that it here it brings out my
eyes more if it's here you know it's bringing off a
different part of my body my chest area you know you can
highlight different parts of your body with the light
I also have this which is basically a phone stand
you can use that one take your content as well
and a clicker so you can connect this to your phone on bluetooth and you just
click and it takes a photo so you can hide it
you don't even know you know that you're you've got it in your hand
so these are really great and all of this stuff I got from either
Amazon team machine so either somewhere like this and it was all
relatively cheap and it does really make a difference when setting up the shot
even this light yeah this is from a place called Azada which is a Thai
Amazon and again it was super cheap so all of this stuff I couldn't
calculate in this moment how much it cost me but
it was it was buttons and it really does make a difference to the shot
so let's have a go at getting into some positions
that could work well for some photos so let's start
on our knees you can adjust your outfit accordingly
fix your hair you know just get yourself feeling
nice and presentable exactly how you want to present yourself
and then we can start on our knees we can open our knees a little bit
we can crawl our hands forward and then like look into the camera
and smile you can give like a sultry lock
you can give more of like a dominate and look by like tailing your head back
or more innocent by like you know pairing for your hair
so yeah that's one poll you could try oh while we're here
on these we can tilt our body to the side
to choose whatever side feels best at you this feels best to me
and then we can angle our body so we're trying to create like a
kind of a half moon here
and put our hands in our hair
eyes if you want to sometimes when I'm shooting I like to just
do something you know do the pose and then just take a breath
and just allow yourself to relax into it more because
sometimes you can be trying to do everything and get all tense and not
actually look you know look soft and look like
at ease which is what you want you don't want to look tense
so you can try one a little bit closer as well to the camera
come really close in I think photos like this are good for the profile
so because it really shows you and so you can get really close you can like
push your cleavage together if you want to
pull it down you can like play with your outfit
you know you can just be playful so yeah that might be a nice one to try
just coming up close to the camera and something you can actually do as well
you can take videos and then just take screenshots of the video
I think this is a really good trick because you capture those moments
that photograph wouldn't just like the in between you know which I think that
those shots can look really great so yeah that could be something to try as
well so think about what your best asset is
and then we can emphasize that in the shot
so let's say your legs are your best asset
the last pose is that we don't really show that so let's try one for the legs
so you want to light back bring your legs towards the camera because
remember whatever's closest to the camera
is going to be bigger so of course my head
look really small back here but my legs are fully in shot so this is what we
want is also it's good to put heels on if you're
doing any photos if that's part of your persona
someone who would wear heels because I think it just elongates the leg
so yeah so you can do shots like this if your legs are
maybe one bent one straight
maybe both straight looking into the camera
can also do something like this to emphasize the legs
these ones but guys would love anyone who's into heels
so yeah that's something you can do okay so let's say our best asset is our
one let's do some booty shots so on that I like
it's kind of bent over on all fours so legs
quite spread apart hands forward so close to the camera
arch in your back
and just come into whatever position feels good to you copy up here
some cute ones you can again play with your outfit
play with your hand positioning and then we can also do some a little bit
lower
so now if I had my clicker I could just have it in my hand
and you don't even see it click click click click click click click click
you know
another good booty shot is like lion
completely flat on the stomach
legs bent and arch the back
click click click so we can also make use of props
and photos so here are some that I had to hand
so I've got a whip so you can have photos holding it
bringing it close to the camera you can use it in a video of course
because it's you know it's dynamic it's moving so it'd be great for the video
but um it's also good for a shot you know you can hold it
in all different ways
showing some ideas
you can also be cheeky
hold it on your bottom
if that fits your persona you can use that or on the flip side
if you're more of a sub on cam the whip would be more for a dom
or even for a sub if you were to whip yourself you could use it for that
but you could also even use rope as well as a prop
I just had some of this rope knocking round so I thought it would look nice as
a prop
you can obviously bound your own hands of it
you know make it look like you're all tied up
you know like this kind of a thing
that'll look good as a as a saw or even as a dom kind of to show power
I don't know like you could
I'm just playing here guys and just seeing what's happening
but yeah that's the good thing about props you can play around with it and see
what works you could even tie yourself up a little bit with it
tie it around the body you know just just play with it
and one final thing is it's good to have something like this for
when taking content like a rope or even just a shirt
just anything that you can put over your shoulders
and again use this kind of a prop you know to like play around with
kind of thing and it'd be good for the video because you can
slowly you know reveal different parts of the body and
use it whatever way you wish like that
speaking the props here's a photo of one of our lovely members at one of our
recent shoots using a book as a prop she's not wearing anything on top but
the book is completely covering hair and this type of a shot could work well
here profile especially if she is trying to cater to
more intellectual clients so now I thought I would go through
some photos of our members and mentors from previous shoots
although these were all taken by a professional photographer
you can still mimic these poses at home yourself
and take inspiration from the photos for example in this one you can see that
Chloe is using a lollipop as a prop and she's modelling head to toe as you
can see her hand that is not holding the lollipop
is pulling on her pants if that was just hanging limp
by her leg it would look like a completely different shot
as in this shot every part of her body is doing something
um so yeah remember that when you're doing your photos
and here's another shot of our lovely Chloe in this one she's using a whip
as a prop as you can see she's got it dangling down her back to her bum
this one you can recreate yourself by setting up the phone or camera
turning around using the best shot that we said before
or using a clicker so in this one Chloe's got on a Santa Alpha
and she's also using it as a prop as you can see she's holding
the hat so this is something that you can do
and for Christmas Valentine's Day, birthday, Halloween
you can get some outfits and dress up so in this shot Sophie is using a laptop
as a prop so this is a great prop to use when taking
photos for your profile as it kind of gives the clients a bit of an insight
as to what you'll look like when you're on cam with them
so this shot of the beautiful Sami is very easy to recreate
you want to be in a dark room but have a spotlight on you
you're going to want to have the camera placed above you
so it's looking down on you and then you can just lie down
and again use your clicker or the best mode to take the photos
so this one would look a bit different to the one before of Sami lying down
so for this shot you wouldn't have the camera angled above you
like in the previous shot as that way you wouldn't get to see the lovely arch
in Chloe's back there so what you would do is you would have the camera angled
on the exact same level as you and then you'll lie on your side
arch your back stretch your arms out you can bend your legs like Chloe is or
you
can even stretch out your legs or try bending one stretch in one
see what works best for you and your body so yeah that's how you'd recreate
this
lovely shot so another one lying down but this
time on our front but everything else can stay the same
that you would have done for the previous shot
so having the camera angled on the same level as you
is absolutely fine for this shot I absolutely love this shot of Sophie
I feel as though she looks super powerful as you can see she's making
full use of the space around here she has her hands on each side
and she's looking directly at the camera and given a really
intense stare and this is a great example to show how
using the space around you can really complete the shot
final photo of one of our lovely members this one would probably be a little
bit
more difficult to recreate yourself but it can still be done
so for this one you're going to want a camera stand phone stand or a ring light
so you can actually stand up the camera or phone whatever you're using
you're going to want to make sure that it's angled
so you could see yourself in the reflection but not the phone
and then again you can just use the clicker or the bea stop
to take photos until you get the right shot
so that brings us to the end of today's video I truly hope that you got
something out of it that you got some tips to use for when you're
taking content and as always let us know what you'd
like to see next and I'll see you on the next video